So fulfill user intent,
創造的にメールを使って
using email creatively, so as to delight the users.
ユーザーの目的をかなえ ユーザーを喜ばせましょう
The ability to have machine learning to scale, to be personalized,
機械学習でスケーリングや パーソナライズを行えれば
gives you lots of opportunities,
さまざまな可能性が生まれ
to use ML creatively and delight your users.
MLを創造的に使って ユーザーを喜ばせることができます
For ML to be magic,
MLを素晴らしいものにするためには
you should keep in mind the word delight,
喜びを忘れてはいけません
delight your users, anticipate their next need.
次に何が必要か予想して ユーザーを喜ばせましょう
Did the card get canceled?
クレジットカードが無効になりましたか？
Did the flight get delayed?
フライトが遅れていますか？
Etc, or did they just walk into your store and see an empty shelf?
あなたのお店で商品が在庫切れでしたか？
Why are they contacting you?
なぜあなたに連絡したのでしょうか？
Did your system automatically find the right action to take for this customer?
システムはこの顧客に対する正しい対応を 自動的に見つけましたか？
Did it offer to re book them?
再予約を提案しましたか？
Offer them a meal voucher,
食券を発行したり
suggested you're happy they're wearing your brand of sneakers.
自社ブランドのスニーカーの 着用に感謝を述べましたか？
Understand the context, that your user is working with them,
ユーザーがどのような状況なのかを把握し
and anticipate their next need.
次に何が必要か予測します
So fulfill user intent in interesting ways,
MLの能力を使い 独創的な方法で
using capabilities of ML.
ユーザーの目的を満たします
For example, users want background music in their videos,
たとえば 動画にBGMを挿入したくても
but using popular songs is a copyright violation, solution?
人気の曲は著作権法違反になります どうしますか？
What if you generate music according to their specs,
条件を満たす音楽を作ったらどうでしょう
if they say they want a climax two and a half minutes in,
開始後2分半にクライマックス
and they want music in a jazz style,
ジャズ風 などのリクエストに応じ
why don't you go ahead and generate that music,
音楽を作りましょう
and use that as a background for your videos.
それを動画のBGMにします
That's not possible with machine learning.
これは機械学習では不可能です
So your business can benefit from machine learning, three ways,
機械学習は3通りの方法で ビジネスに貢献します
one infuse your applications with machine learning,
1つ目は 機械学習をアプリに組み込み
simplify the user input,
ユーザー入力を簡素化し
adapt to the user.
ユーザーに適合することです
Second, use machine learning to fine tune your business,
2つ目は 機械学習によってビジネスを微調整し
to streamline your business processes,
事業過程を合理化することで
maybe even create new business opportunities,
新しいビジネスチャンスが 生まれるかもしれません
and finally, use machine learning to delight your users,
最後に 機械学習でユーザーを喜ばせ
anticipate their needs, and use machine learning to
何が必要かを予測することで
creatively fulfill what the user intended to do.
独創的な方法でユーザーの目的を 満たすことができるのです